katagogi.com 2012-10-15

# Family tree

|  | 

Privacy Policy  
  
---  
  
INTRODUCTION   
  
Katagogi.com recognizes the confidentiality of information that may be disclosed by members in registering to our Website and is committed to protecting any data that we collect concerning you. By using our services, you agree to the use of the data that we collect in accordance with this Privacy Policy.  

PROTECTING YOUR PRIVACY  
We collect the minimum amount of information about you that is commensurate with providing you with a satisfactory service. This Policy indicates the type of processes that may result in data being collected about you. Your use of this website gives us the right to collect that information.  
  
INFORMATION COLLECTED  
  
We may collect any or all of the information that you give us depending on the type of transaction you enter into, including your name, address, telephone number, fax number and email address, together with data about your use of the website. Other information that may be needed from time to time to process a request may also be collected as indicated on the website.   

INFORMATION USE  
  
Katagogi.com uses the information collected primarily to process the task for which you visited the website. All reasonable precautions are taken to prevent unauthorized access to this information. This safeguard may require you to provide additional forms of identity should you wish to obtain information about your account details.  

"IP ADDRESSES" AND COOKIES   
We do use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Website.   
Your Internet browser has the in-built facility for storing small files - "cookies" - that hold information which allows a website to recognize your account. Our website takes advantage of this facility to enhance your experience.   
  
DISCLOSING INFORMATION   
We do not disclose any personal information obtained about you from this website to third parties except when we need to do so in order to complete the transaction. We may also use the information to keep in contact with you and inform you of developments associated with our business. You will be given the opportunity to remove yourself from any mailing list or similar device. If at any time in the future we should wish to disclose information collected on this website to any third party, it would only be with your knowledge and consent.   
We may from time to time provide information of a general nature to third parties - for example, the number of individuals visiting our website or completing a registration form, but we will not use any information that could identify those individuals.   
  
LINKED WEBSITE   
  
The contents of any websites linked from or to Katagogi.com are managed by the respective parties or entities that administer those websites and are not controlled by Katagogi.com. Use each linked websites under the terms and conditions clearly stipulated by the respective party. We shall not be held responsible for the contents of any linked websites or any damages arising from the use of linked websites.   

DIRECT MAILING   
  
Katagogi.com will send electronic mail to you, for the purpose of informing you of changes or additions to Katagogi.com. If you do not want to receive such mailings, you may opt out at any time by using the unsubscribe link listed in the e-mail or at your preferences page.   

CHANGES TO THE POLICY   
  
Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be placed here and will supersede this version of our Policy. We will take reasonable steps to draw your attention to any changes in our Policy. However, to be on the safe side, we suggest that you read this document each time you use the website to ensure that it still meets with your approval.  

MEMBER PROFILES  
  
You may provide information about yourself to the community and other areas of our Website, but only at your option. If provided in a public community area, the data is, of course, public. Participation in public areas and community services is at your discretion. 

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, if you want to know what information we have collected about you, or if you want to inquire with us about this Website use the Inquiry Form.
